{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Isometric drawings are often used by ________ to help illustrate complex designs.", "opta": "mechanical engineers", "optb": "piping drafters", "optc": "aerospace engineers", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In order to create an isometric circle to represent a hole through the top surface of a box, the drafter must insure that the correct isoplane has been selected by scrolling through the isoplanes using the ________ key.", "opta": "F1", "optb": "F3", "optc": "F5", "optd": "F8", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A fillet is a rounded surface on the ________ corner of a part.", "opta": "Inside", "optb": "outside", "optc": "radial", "optd": "isoplane", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Before starting an isometric drawing in AutoCAD the drafter needs to ________.", "opta": "set the grid to isometric", "optb": "set the current layer to Defpoints", "optc": "turn Object Snap off", "optd": "turn Ortho off", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A round is a rounded surface on the ________ corner of a part.", "opta": "inside", "optb": "outside", "optc": "radial", "optd": "isoplane", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Architectural drafters generally prefer to use ________ drawings to help illustrate 3-dimensional views of a structure.", "opta": "isometric", "optb": "perspective", "optc": "orthographic", "optd": "auxiliary", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The bounding box method for setting up an isometric drawing helps the drafter ________.", "opta": "confine the isometric drawing to its maximum size", "optb": "figure what lines are to be illustrated vertical and horizontal", "optc": "position the isometric drawing in paper space", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The Offset tool should only be used for placing ________ in an isometric drawing.", "opta": "circles", "optb": "horizontal lines", "optc": "vertical lines", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When creating an isometric drawing in AutoCAD the drafter can utilize the Dynamic Input and Polar Coordinate system to place both vertical and horizontal lines. A line created from one point 3 inches at 180 degrees would be a ________ line.", "opta": "horizontal", "optb": "vertical", "optc": "inclined", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "AutoCAD refers to isometric ellipses as ________.", "opta": "Ellipses", "optb": "isoellipses", "optc": "isocircles", "optd": "circles", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}